ibollytv.com 2013-09-14

# Privacy Policy - ibollytv.com

## **Privacy Policy - http://www.ibollytv.com**

At www.ibollytv.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.ibollytv.com and how it is used. 

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, http://www.ibollytv.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user�s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Use of Cookies and Web Beacons**

Like other major Websites, http://www.ibollytv.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on http://www.ibollytv.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

http://www.ibollytv.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. http://www.ibollytv.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

**Tell Friends**

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend or friends about our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. We will automatically send the friend a one-time email invitation to visit the site. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending these emails. The friend may contact us at contact.ibollytv AT gmail DOT com to request the removal of this information from our database.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

We frequently revise this Privacy Policy to keep it up to date with ibollytv Web pages. "Updated" may be used to alert users to recent changes and to the date of the last update.

**No Error Free Performance**

We customarily release alpha and beta versions of our products, which are further refined before the release of the final "Gold" version. Because these products are still in a test phase, we may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our efforts to do so. As such, we welcome feedback on any privacy concerns you may have, and on how to improve our products generally, in all stages of release. ibollytv does not guarantee error-free performance under this privacy policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this privacy policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with our privacy policy. ibollytv shall not be liable for any incidental, consequential or punitive damages relating to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy shall be governed by the laws of the United States. 

**Contact Us about Privacy**

CONTACT US ABOUT PRIVACY If you have questions about the privacy aspects of our products or services or would like to make a complaint, please contact at contact.ibollytv AT gmail DOT COM.

Privacy Policy Group  
www.ibollytv.com

Copyright © 2013 www.ibollytv.com.
